Yes, I am the first.
No, no.
Oh, this can't be true.
So why are we here?
To find the source of greenhouse gases.
Oh, yeah.
Do you think we'll find any?
Actually, that could be it.
Okay.
So I found the first source.
The car.
One way could to ride a bike
more often or use public transport.
What you need to know is carbon
is also a natural cycle.
It enters and leaves the atmosphere
constantly.
The oceans, for example, they are
large carbon storages, forests as well
as the soil, and of course, Yes.
Everyone releases carbon
into the atmosphere.
But seriously,
there's still big pollutants.
No, because nature is perfect.
The oceans, forests, and soil also store
carbon, and in the end, it balances out.
It's a cycle.
That ensures there's always a bit
of greenhouse gas in the atmosphere.
Remember, we need it.
And voila.
Let me introduce my new factory
for making super modern, ultra trendy,
extremely high tech products.
And how do we write that now?
But no, your factory needs energy,
so it surely burns oil.
Yes, but like I told you,
she makes such great stuff.
Well, I'm not sure We need that.
Don't count on me to buy them.
I have an idea.
They say trees are carbon sinks,
meaning they can store more.
If I add trees, that balances out.
But why are you doing that?
The workers of my factory are hungry.
I need space to grow grain,
and I also keep cattle for meat.
But now, the balance is totally off.
The trees you cut down
no longer absorb carbon.
When they die, they even release some.
Oh, and look at the oxen.
They have flatulence.
The livestock release methane,
another greenhouse gas.
Look, that disturbs the balance.
The packaging.
Yes.
A lot of energy and resources
are needed to make packaging.
This naturally has a carbon impact.
So we should choose products
with as little packaging as possible.
Oh, look, French cheese.
Wait.
Did you test it?
We're in the USA,
but this cheese is from France.
It has travelled thousands
of kilometres, just like us.
No, but he might have hitchhiked.
More likely by plane or a big ship.
Very environmentally harmful
means of prompting.
Should we eat products
that come from nearby?
We need to hurry back to France to tell
the others everything we've discovered.