We arrived in Germany.
I'm exhausted.
What a migration.
Look, I found us a great pigeon hotel.
Look at everything there is.
Quickly, I turn on the oven
to heat some seeds.
Look at the German countryside.
It's beautiful.
There are even wind turbines
that produce renewable energy.
Oh, look, we can make milkshakes.
Oh, a popcorn machine.
I'm going to take a shower, too.
Look at this giant TV.
I'm going to put some
heat on for my shower.
Hugo, stop.
Turn off the devices.
You do not realise.
To operate all of these devices,
you have to produce energy.
But you told me they used wind turbines.
They work with the wind.
It's an energy that never disappears.
But that's just part of it.
In Germany, renewable energies
represent 44%, which is less than half.
But I can't only turn on half of the TV.
In the In the world,
renewable energies only represent 20%.
This means that for the vast
majority, we use fossil fuels
which took millions of years to create.
Like oil, gas?
Yes, and they release a lot
of greenhouse gases when we use them.
Is that what's making our planet hot?
What if we went to see a country
that uses 100% renewable energy?
It exists.