You could have warned me that
we were going to do 2000 kilometres.
Well, Iceland is definitely not next door.
All the more reason to warn.
I was wrong.
I took a room without a TV.
Quick, we have to go again.
Wait, what if we made board games instead?
It's fun, and what's more,
it doesn't use electricity.
We actually came here because Iceland
Is a country that only produces
its electricity with renewable energies.
They don't burn oil?
Mm-hmm.
They don't burn gas?
Mm-mm.
But I don't even see any wind turbines.
How do they do it?
Iceland is a country
with many mountains and rivers.
As a result, they produce 73% of
their electricity with hydropower plants.
To create electricity,
it's always the same thing.
You have to succeed in turning a turbine.
The dam sends water down
the mountain in a long tight.
The water arrives so quick
that it turns the turbine upon arrival.
And since the river always brings water.
That's why we say it's a renewable energy.
For the rest, they use
heat from the ground.
It's called geothermal energy.
Deep down, the ground is warm.
As a result, they send the water deep.
It heats naturally and comes up very
hot, sometimes in steam.
This water, naturally heated
by our planet, becomes steam.
It rises so quickly that it also turns
a turbine which produces electricity.
But Iceland is a small country.
There are only 370,000 inhabitants.
Electric needs are low.
It must be easier to do
without fossil fuels.
It's true, and not all
countries can have dams.
Maybe residents also need
to change their habits.
That's to say, now?
Quick, let's go back to Germany.
But we didn't sleep.