Here we are, back in Germany.
My favourite room.
You see, Mori, progress, modernity,
what differentiates us from the caveman?
That's it.
What if we turned off the TV
to reduce electricity?
Oh, no.
Don't take away the TV.
Oh, you saw.
It had a positive impact.
Great.
Here we go for a world without TV.
Your world is going to be great, Maury.
Because you didn't like the
board game night we had in Iceland.
Oh, yes.
We had a lot of fun.
I'm not saying we should remove the TV,
but not leaving it on when you're not
looking at it and reducing
its use is already interesting.
Oh, I have another idea.
How about you wear a sweater?
What if we turn down the heating
and we could take shorter showers
to use less hot water?
No, that's too much.
Welcome to the Middle Ages.
Your ideas make me depressed.
But are you cold?
No.
So what's the problem?
Well, the colour.
I don't like the colour of the sweater.
We can find you another one.
But It's true that it works.
Could we also instal better
insulated windows to reduce
the energy need for heating?
We could also get around
a lot more on a bike or on foot.
That's better.
Okay, it's becoming a world
that makes you want to.
Basically, on the one hand, we
must develop renewable energies and on
the other hand, reduce our consumption.
Without this, it will become depressing.
Exactly.
For me, it's more a polluted world
that makes me depressed.
Oh, I still have lots of ideas
for reducing energy consumption.